戴立克疯人院·前传
编剧：史蒂文·莫法特
我好像没有请你过来坐
I don't think I asked you to sit.
有个女人想要见你
There is a woman who wants to meet you.
真是好事 但是我已经结婚了
That's nice. but I am married.
她需要你的帮助
Your help is required.
我从不在公共场合谈论正事
I never discuss my business in public.
我知道
I know.
你是谁
Who are you?
一个信使
A messenger.
谁的信使
Who's messenger?
达拉·冯·卡森
Darla Von Karlsen
从没听过她
Never heard of her.
茶室去哪儿了
Where's the tea room?
你从一开始就不在茶室里
You are never in the tea room.
对 当然了
Oh, of course.
心灵投影
Psychic projection.
有人给我发了个梦中消息
Someone sent me a dream message.
这样的话 希望我睡在一个舒服的地方
Well, I hope I fell asleep somewhere comfy.
请识别出你所在之处
Do recognize where you are.
不记得了
Can't remember.
要怎么挂断在这玩意儿
How do you hang up on this thing.
你不能
You can't.
是吗
Oh, yeah?
如果我直接醒来呢
And what if I just wake up.
不 博士
No, Doctor.
海滩也不是真的
The beach isn't real either.
你仍然在梦中
You are still dreaming.
时空坐标
Space-time coordinates.
你要在这里与达拉·冯·卡森见面
You will meet Darla Von Karlsen here.
她的女儿处于危险之中
Her daughter is in danger.
只有你能救她
Only you can save her.
你认识这个星球
You recognize the planet.
是的
Yes.
说出来
Say it.
不
No.
说出星球的名字
Name the planet.
我绝不会说出那个名字
I will not say that name.
说出来  不
- Say it! - No!
说出星球的名字 说出来
Name the planet. Name the planet.
斯卡洛
Skaro.